Now that we've covered walking properly, lets work on focusing on One Point, so we're actually moving up the body as we go.
One Point, if you could look, the center of mass, is going to be bellybutton, anywhere from 2 to 3 inches down, depending, so right about where this belt is.
Now One Point is the principal of dynamic motion without actual visible motion taking place.
One way of thinking of it is that, if you have somebody, it's tensile strength.
And if you have somebody grab onto your arm, they're out to be a living, breathing connection, that, yes they're, it feels very strong, it feels like a fire hose.
A fire hose is almost impossible to bend when water is flowing through it.
It's a living entity, and therefore, One Point is very much the same thing, it is a living entity.
And you are looking for that constant relaxed, natural power of tensile strength.
It's not muscular by any means, and it is certainly not structural, but there is, well I shouldn't say that, because there is an aspect of structural to it.
With correct structure, and correct relaxation, you build on tensile strength.
And we will continue on this subject, shortly thereafter.